ncsecu.org 2016-04-22

# FACTS

                                                                                                                  Rev. 4/2014
                       WHAT DOES STATE EMPLOYEES’ CREDIT UNION (SECU)
   FACTS               DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                   Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                       consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
                       how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                       understand what we do.
What?                 The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or services you
                      have with us. This information can include:
                                 Social Security number and income
                                 Account balances and payment history
                                 Account transactions and mortgage rates and payments
                      When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this
                       notice.
How?                   All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday
                       business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                       members’ personal information; the reasons State Employees’ Credit Union chooses to share;
                       and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information                 Does SECU Share?                Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes –
such as to process your transactions, maintain
your account(s), respond to court orders and legal                       Yes                                No
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes –
to offer our products and services to you                                Yes                                No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
                                                                         Yes                                No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
information about your transactions and experiences                      Yes                                No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
information about your creditworthiness                                   No                          We don’t share
For nonaffiliates to market to you
                                                                          No                          We don’t share
    Questions?                Call 888-732-8562 or go to www.ncsecu.org

Page 2
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?    State Employees’ Credit Union and SECU*RE, Inc.
What we do
How does SECU                    To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
protect my personal information? and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
                                 These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                                 and buildings.
How does SECU                    We collect your personal information, for example, when you
collect my personal information?
                                     open an account or deposit money
                                     pay your bills or apply for a loan
                                     use your credit or debit card
                                 We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                 bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?   Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                     sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information
                                      about your creditworthiness
                                     affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                     sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                 State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                 limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                       Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                 financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                     Our affiliates include: SECU*RE, Inc.; SECU Life Insurance Co.;
                                      Credit Union Investment Services; and SECU Brokerage Services
Nonaffiliates                    Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                 financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                     SECU does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing                  A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                 together market financial products or services to you.
                                     Our joint marketing partners include insurance and financial
                                      services companies.
